Rest in pieces.
LEGO Star Wars Terrifying Tales is a animation, family,
science fiction film directed by Ken Cunningham.
Poe Dameron and BB-8 must face the greedy crime boss Graballa the Hutt, who has purchased Darth Vader’s
castle and is renovating it into the galaxy’s first all-inclusive Sith-inspired luxury hotel.
Poe Dameron / Motti (voice), played by Jake Green.
Dean (voice), played by Raphael Alejandro.
Graballa the Hutt (voice), played by Dana Snyder.
Vaneé (voice), played by Tony Hale.
Ren (voice), played by Christian Slater.
Darth Vader (voice), played by Matt Sloan.
Lego Star Wars: Terrifying Tales is a 2021 animated special based on the Star Wars franchise,
and produced by Lucasfilm Animation and The Lego Group alongside Atomic Cartoons.
Like The Lego Star Wars Holiday Special, it is directed by Ken
Cunningham from a script written by David Shayne.
A stand-alone sequel to the Star Wars sequel trilogy, the
special was released on Disney+ on October 1, 2021.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.